EMMANUEL SASERE

FRONTEND ENGINEER









SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated frontend engineer with a passion for creating intuitive and visually appealing user interfaces. Despite having less than one year of experience in the field, I am dedicated to delivering high-quality solutions. I have a keen eye for design and am committed to staying updated with the latest trends in frontend development. I am eager to collaborate, innovate, and contribute to meaningful projects in the digital realm.

SKILLS

- Html, CSS
- React.Js
- WordPress
- JavaScript
- Tailwind Css

SKILLS

- Strong problem-solving
- Analytical skills
- Collaboration
- Critical thinking
- Attention to detail
- Communication

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bond Synergy Holdings

Software Developer • 2023 - Present

- Developed websites to boost digital presence and drive business growth.
- Collaborated with external senior developers to innovate digital solutions.
- Contributed to launching and maintaining digital initiatives.
- Provided insights to enhance the company's digital strategy.
- Demonstrated strong problem-solving and attention to detail.
- www.bondsynergyholdings.com

Study Stern

Software Developer • 2024

- Developed and launched a waitlist feature for Study Stern.
- Collaborated with team members on feature development.
- Ensured feature met high quality and functionality standards.
- Contributed ideas to enhance the waitlist and product.
- Demonstrated strong teamwork and communication skills.
- www.studystern.com

Broken But Not Shattered Group

Web Developer • Oct 2023-Nov 2023

- Designed and developed a WordPress website for Broken But Not Shattered.
- Created and executed a campaign to drive traffic to the website.
- Ensured the website reflected the organization's mission and values.
- Monitored campaign performance and made adjustments as needed.
- www.brokenbutnotshattered.org

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Miva Open University • 2024-present

Full Stack Web development Nabteb Certificate

Ekobits Academy • 2022 - 2023

CERTIFICATIONS

CS50 Certificate Of Completion

Edx • Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

Zero To Mastery(Python) Certificate Of Completion

Udemy | Jan 2021 - Jun 2021